I need you in my party, got it?
[gasps]
I hope you'll keep
lending me your strength.
♪
[grunts]
[panting]
Dice Thrust!
[grunts]
[gasps]
[Ruche yells]
[straining]
[squeals excitedly]
[gasps, chuckles]
-[Ruche grunts]
-[AUTOMATED VOICE] Critical.
[Ruche grunts]
♪
[grunts]
[Golden Raana croaks]
[thuds]
[clinking]
[ELYMAS] It's nice that
Golden Raana
-are worth a lot of EXP.
-[Ruche gasps]
But the best part
is the valuable items
they can drop.
The drop rate is right at 50%.
[gasps]
[squeals excitedly]
[chuckles excitedly]
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Dazzling Raana Decorative Blade.
Attack, plus 12.
Market price, 17 million gold.
A glittering Raana short sword.
A hunk
of high-purity Raana gold.
[squeals excitedly]
A Dazzling Raana
Decorative Blade!
[♪ opening theme song playing]
Wow. I can't believe
how easily we acquired
a 1,700,000 gold item!
[ELYMAS] Hold on.
You're actually missing a digit.
Add a zero to that.
Huh?
The item's worth 17 million.
Uh...
[Ruche chuckles nervously]
One, two, three, four.
Wait. You're right. That's 17.
[whimpering weakly]
[stifled gasp]
[RUCHE] My old party
ended up kicking me
because I wanted my share
of that Blood-Soaked Sword.
And it was
only worth two million.
Have you calmed down
a little bit?
Yeah, I think so.
Um. That said,
it was pretty shocking.
Look at how simple it was for us
to obtain something so valuable.
Maybe that's odd for me
to say after you set this up,
but I still don't understand
how we did it.
[gasps]
Wait! Carrying around
something rare like this
is going to
make us huge targets!
Come on!
Let's run away together!
We'll hide out
in some remote place
where we won't be found!
Yes, that's what we should do.
Yup, yup, yup.
-[Elymas chuckles softly]
-[Ruche whimpering]
Well.
You're not wrong.
We need to get going.
Before the sun goes down,
we'll farm one more.
What? You're kidding, right?
[chuckles softly]
[ELYMAS] Three hours later.
-And Dice Thrust!
-[AUTOMATED VOICE] Miss.
-Let's go, Dice Thrust!
-Dice Thrust time!
-[AUTOMATED VOICE] Miss.
-How 'bout now?
Just work already!
[AUTOMATED VOICE] Miss.
This is it! Now Dice Thrust!
♪
[Ruche grunts]
[AUTOMATED VOICE] Critical.
Well done! That's two!
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Level 33 has been reached.
-[Ruche whimpering]
-[ELYMAS] Ruche?
-Uh.
-[Ruche sobbing]
[crying]
Uh, hey. Come on. No big deal.
So maybe you missed a few times.
That just means you're saving
your luck for later.
♪
[RUCHE] 30--
[chuckles]
Thirty-four million.
-[chuckles in disbelief]
-[Elymas gasps]
Uh, Ruche?
Pull yourself together!
It's all right!
Ruche!
[Ruche laughing incredulously]
♪
It's just so much.
These are worth millions
upon millions of gold.
Thanks to your skills,
we've gathered two Dazzling
Raana Decorative Blades.
And soon we'll need to determine
the most effective use
of this money.
For our party's sake,
we need to start planning
and choose well.
[RUCHE] Right. I agree.
We have to start thinking more
about our future.
But none of this
feels real to me.
It's weird.
[ELYMAS] We should consider
our current equipment
when deciding how
to spend our skill points.
[RUCHE] Oh, yeah!
I've been leveling up a lot,
so that means I still have
plenty of skill points
I haven't even used yet.
How should I spend them all?
Mm. You really ought
to keep that private
and not show other people.
Ah, now don't you worry.
I owe you! Nobody else
could've helped me come this far
and gotten me
to such a high level!
So you could even use me up.
And then toss me aside,
and I still wouldn't mind.
[chuckles nervously]
I'm pretty sure
I'd feel even worse
if you didn't care at all.
Mm?
[gasps]
Hey, what is it?
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[Ruche gasps]
A voice.
-Voice?
-Mm?
Yes. It sounded like
a baby was crying
way off in the distance.
Uh! [gasps]
A crying baby?
[Elymas gasps]
Could it be?
-It's wandering now.
-[gasps]
[ELYMAS] A dungeon's boss,
called its Dreamlord,
is essentially its heart.
Normally, it remains
deep within its walls.
But sometimes, it ventures out
and roams around
the other levels as well.
It's known as wandering.
So, it's just loose?!
Isn't this Dreamlord meant
for adventurers at Level 50?!
-That doesn't sound so good.
-We're fine.
If we take the right steps,
I'm certain we can avoid it.
We need to start
moving away from the voice
and straight for the exit.
The Dreamlord
won't follow us outside.
Then it isn't gonna chase us?
What a load off my mind.
[ELYMAS] Yeah. There's really
nothing to it at all.
We'll make our way out of here,
then head back to town
and cash in our loot.
At least that's where
this adventure of ours
should have ended.
But...
Help us! Please!
[gasps]
[both adventurers panting]
[ELYMAS] I was just being naive.
We were fighting a monster,
and then a much more
powerful one showed up!
It was too strong for us!
[Ruche whimpering]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[both panting]
[ELYMAS] This isn't a game
we're playing.
[MAN] Stay with me!
[ELYMAS] Those two will never
get out of here like that.
It just appeared.
[ELYMAS] We can't leave
this dungeon now.
If we try to escape,
they'll definitely die!
[grunts]
Listen!
You need to take them both
outside right away!
While I keep
the monster occupied!
[RUCHE] Okay, but you realize
that not even someone
as strong as you can handle
a Level 50 Dreamlord, right?!
[ELYMAS] I understand
how it behaves,
so I can buy some time
for you three
and escape by myself.
-Besides...
-Uh.
[gasps]
... as a Heavy Knight,
it's my job to draw aggro.
Mr. Elymas.
[grunts tensely]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[Ruche squeals in fright]
[both whimpering]
[ELYMAS] There you are.
[footsteps approaching]
[ELYMAS] Tin Knight.
[both adventurers panting]
Help us! Please!
-[both gasp]
-We were fighting a monster,
and then a much more
powerful one showed up!
[woman coughs]
[ELYMAS] This isn't a game
we're playing.
[both panting]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Ruche squeals in fright]
[both whimpering]
I'll take it from here!
Now go! Get them outside.
Wait. Hang on.
Sir, thank you.
Thank you for helping us.
[gasps]
Look at that.
It's sustained some damage.
The situation
could be a lot worse.
[gasps]
All right.
That creature may seem powerful,
but it's been weakened.
Let's defeat it together!
-[ELYMAS] No. Not this time.
-[gasps]
-You must run.
-[RUCHE] I wanna help!
This is a Tin Knight,
-not the Dreamlord itself.
-[gasps]
They're only
the creature's minions.
But soon, it will be here.
[gasps]
[Ruche gasps]
No way. [whimpers]
Now he's up against
three Level 40s?
[ELYMAS] I'll be right
behind you, just as soon as
-I've bought some time.
-You can't!
And it wouldn't be right
for me to run off
and let you fight them
all by yourself!
Not after you invited me
to join your party.
Do you really want me
to spell it out for you?!
I can't carry dead weight
while I'm fighting these guys.
You'd just get in the way.
Understand?
[gasps]
[whimpers]
Yeah. You're right.
I'm sorry.
[Elymas grunts]
Well, just don't take too long,
Mr. Elymas.
[grunts]
[ELYMAS] Three Level 40s, huh?
If Ruche had stayed back here,
and we'd battled them together,
the two of us might have
been able to defeat them.
[grunts]
But...
[baby crying]
The Dreamlord
is still out there.
I told her
I would draw them to me
and then run
when I got the chance,
but that was a lie.
As a Heavy Knight,
I don't have any speed.
I might be able
to escape a few Tin Knights.
But trying to run
from a dungeon boss
who's using magic attacks?
[baby crying]
That's impossible.
[snarling]
I'll have to defeat
this Dreamlord right here.
There you are, Dreamlord Embryo!
[Embryo crying]
[ELYMAS] For a Level 50 monster,
the Embryo's stats
are fairly low.
The problem is, I won't be able
to deal damage to it.
Its flesh's Defense
is far too high
for my attacks to get through.
Only its eye
is truly vulnerable.
And it's not an easy target.
Reaching it requires
ranged attacks.
But if it's got a weakness,
then even a low-level adventurer
can take it down.
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Oath of the Heavy Armor
has reached Level 27.
New skill acquired. Shield Bash.
It's your move, Embryo!
I won't run!
I'm ready to battle you head-on!
Shield Bash!
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Skill, Shield Bash.
Push an enemy with a shield
and knock them back.
[ELYMAS]
Good thing I have a skill
that lets me split up
my enemies.
Parry!
[grunts] Disarm!
The Embryo has
two magic attacks,
Sylph Cutter and Thunderstorm.
But it won't use either
if the Tin Knights
are in their path.
Which means
I can focus on these three!
[grunts]
[panting, grunting]
[grunts] Disarm!
That's the second hit.
It's only been 47 seconds
since the first Disarm.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
I've met
the activation conditions.
[grunts]
Rampart Reflection!
The real battle starts now.
That's one down.
Still.
[Embryo babbles]
[gasps]
If I'm not able
to defeat the Embryo,
the Tin Knights will just
keep getting revived.
[Embryo babbles happily]
But I've noticed
each time it uses its magic,
its eye is completely exposed.
[grunts]
Take this!
[cries in pain]
[ELYMAS] It's the one attack
I've got
that can actually reach it.
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Earth Magic Stone.
Spend MP to fire
countless needles of earth.
[crying]
[ELYMAS] I can use
the Tin Knight as a shield
to protect myself against
its Sylph Cutter attack.
As long as
I don't screw this up,
I'll be able to keep myself
from getting one-shotted.
[grunts]
Shield Bash!
What?
[gasps]
[grunts] Final Slash!
Somehow,
they're beginning to learn.
Monsters could never adapt
to the skills players used
against them in Magic World.
Fighting these three,
it's clear they can recognize
when Shield Bash is coming.
I should have expected this.
It'll make destroying
the Embryo even harder
than I first anticipated.
The only possible way
I'll be able to beat it
is to throw
three more Magic Stones,
but Dreamlords
regenerate very quickly.
If I take too long, I'm screwed.
[gasps]
[Embryo laughs]
[ELYMAS] No way.
It shouldn't use Sylph Cutter
with us positioned like this!
[gasps]
It's no use.
I can't dodge it!
[yelling]
[screams]
[grunting]
[grunts]
[Embryo laughing]
[Elymas grunts]
I'm losing consciousness.
[breathing laboriously]
-[heart thumping]
-My heart
is pounding out of my chest.
And I can feel my legs
growing weaker.
[heart thumping]
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Status effect, Stunned.
[ELYMAS] I see.
In a situation like this,
a stun is fatal.
[straining]
Who knows?
Maybe my starting Luck value
was set too low.
Well, Ruche,
I should have asked you to stay.
Come on.
Let's defeat it together!
[RUCHE] Did ya call for me?
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[straining]
[gasps]
Thanks for asking me
to join your party.
[♪ closing theme song playing]
[ELYMAS] I wasn't overconfident.
I gave everything
I possibly could
to that fight.
But no matter what I tried,
I still wasn't able
to take down
the Dreamlord Embryo.
Then Ruche rescued me,
putting herself in danger
to make sure I was safe.
So now I-- No, we are going
to defeat the Embryo together
and beat this dungeon.
Next time, "Dreamlord."
Ruche is far more
than I ever could have imagined.